在NASA的早期项目中……
In the beginning of the NASA space program...
……火箭越大越好
...bigger was better
搞大新闻，需要大火箭
Big ideas required big rockets
这些大火箭带我们去了我们未曾想过的遥远之境
These big rockets took us farther than we’d ever dreamed possible
先是入轨，接着到了月球
First into orbit, and then to the moon
它们甚至还让我们了解太阳系的边缘，甚至更远
They’ve taken us to the edge of the solar system, and beyond
它们给了我们一双观察宇宙的千里眼
They’ve given us a new perspective on the universe
让我们去探索那遥远的世界
And allowed us to explore distant worlds
当年，宏伟的计划需要巨大的火箭
In the beginning big ideas required big rockets
但今天，随着技术让一切都在变小……
But today, as technology continues to get smaller...
……使得大小不再是阻碍
...size is no longer the limit
下面给大家介绍NASA的冒险级发射服务！
Introducing NASA’s Venture Class Launch Service
火箭虽小……
A smaller class of rocket...
……却让我们比以前更敢想敢做
...inspiring us to think bigger, dream bigger than ever before
冒险级发射服务，小火箭，小团队
Venture Class, smaller rockets designed by smaller teams
让你的载荷……
Dedicated payloads...
……马上就能用……
...faster turnaround...
……只要九九八！
...at a fraction of the cost
就能发射一颗巴掌大的卫星！
Launching satellites you can fit in the palm of your hand
帮助拓宽科学、技术、通信领域
Helping to expand the industries of science, technology, and communication
老百姓买得起的价格，让我们离太空更进一步！
Bringing us closer together by making space more accessible than ever before
大想法……
Big ideas...
更大的梦想……
Bigger dreams...
更小的卫星
In a smaller package
冒险级发射服务 赶紧拿起电话订购吧！
Venture Class